Professional Summary

A highly motivated, flexible and organized professional with a demonstrated ability in customer service, corporate communication skills and implementing innovative solutions in the workplace.

Phone: (213) 343-7580

Skill Summary

Management: Ability to lead while serving company and employees, motivate personnel, and provide support in every area of activity. Secure lasting customer relationships with skills in education of company and products, Budget Management, inventory control, expense tracking and planning, and coordination of employee scheduling and task management.

IT Administration: Active Directory, Hypervisor, vCenter Server Data Center, Windows Server 2008 +, RemoteApps and configuration, NinjaRMM, Connectwise, Windows 7, 8 and 10, some Apple experience, Microsoft Office Suite, Adobe Creative Suite and products, Digital Printing Solutions, Network Administration, computer repair and troubleshooting, and IT Management.

Office Administration: Typing (55+WPM), 10-key; Reception; all office equipment (fax, copier, printer), filing, accounting & billing.

Employment History

Technical Manager

2/8/2016 – Present 1st Choice IT Encino, CA

- Oversee daily technical workload and 10 technical employees.
- Distribute IT support tickets according to employee skill and position.
- Manage large business networks with windows servers and workstations.
- Manage Cloud Servers in Data Center.
- Network traffic optimization and analysis
- Support for specialized medical EMR and billing software, Medisoft and IMS
- Assure PCI and HIPAA compliance with medical and dental customers.
- Remotely support client software and hardware needs and issues.
- Install, support and troubleshoot dental intraoral cameras, sensors and panoramic imaging stations and software.

Warehouse Supervisor

2/15/2015 – 2/8/2016 Lynwood, CA

- Oversee daily warehouse operations.
- Design and implement warehouse standards and procedures.
- Inventory tracking, shipping, receiving on manual system.
- Coordinate workloads and needs with department heads.
- Liquidation sales, auctions and implementation.

Staff Coordinator

9/4/2013 – 1/12/2015 Oaks of Righteousness Ministries (DBA: 5 Breads and 2 Fish) Los Angeles, CA

- Oversee daily warehouse operations: Coordinate work duties and schedules for 10 staff and 250 volunteers
- Conduct Church Services three times a week
- Secure donor relationships, locations, services and products; oversee implementation and logistics
- Truck driver operator: pick-up food product donations at various locations. Forklift and pallet jack operation
- Create and maintain donors and volunteers' databases and manage budget and expense tracking

RecreationalCoordinator

10/2012 – 07/2013 State of California Blythe, CA

- Manage facility and equipment usage for sports and exercise programs: calendar with schedules
- Oversee team and league sports functions and contests
- Maintain inventory, oversee checkout and retrieval of equipment
- Perform janitorial duties and cleanup of facilities: create and process service orders

Jerry A. Brown

350 N. Glendale Ave. Ste B #313, Glendale, CA Phone: (213) 343-7580

jerry.brown1015@gmail.com

In stall at ion Technician

06/2009 – 02/2011 First Mobile Technologies Conshohocken, PA

- Installation of wiring harnesses, docking stations, computers and GPS equipment into fleet vehicles
- Represent Pennsylvania-based company in the Florida and Sothern U.S. Territory
- Client scheduling; Layout Design; Inventory Reconciliation and Shipping & Receiving

(MIS) Management of Information Systems

05/2006 – 02/2009 AutoPics Jacksonville, FL

- Design ad layout, audit weekly books, server administration and computer/network maintenance
- Network traffic optimization and analysis
- Manage staff of 10: met all production deadlines
- Print production responsibilities: layouts, PDF conversions and proofing and file transfers via FTP

Education History

General Educational Development (GED) Certificate

The Complete VMware vSpere 6.5: Beginner to Advanced Certificate

21 years on the job technical training (Owned my own business from 2003-2010 - Cyber System Technologies)